wpdis.co 2012-09-20

# Privacy Policy | WPDis.co - Free And Premium Worpress Themes for Download

Your confidentiality is imperative for us. We have a set of principles; according to which we work. Certainly, you hold the right to ascertain if we are truthful in our claim. Below are the details: 

  * We do not request your private information unless we actually need it. 
  * We can not bear services that ask you for information like your gender or income level for no understandable explanation. 
  * We do not share your personal information with anyone except to meet the terms of law, develop our products, or protect our rights. 
  * We do not collect and save personal information on our servers unless required for the constant process of one of our services. 

Our Privacy policy assimilates following major aims: 

### Website Visitors:

Similar to a good number of website operatives, our system collects non-personally-identifying information of the kind that web browsers and servers typically make accessible, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Our intention in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better comprehend how our visitors use our website. From time to time, we may release non-personally-identifying information in collective form, e.g., by bringing out a report on trend in the usage of our website. 

We also collect potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. We do not utilize such information to identify its visitors and do not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that we use and disclose personally-identifying information, as described below. 

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to our website choose to interact with us in ways that require us to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that our system gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. We collect such information only inasmuch as is essential or suitable to accomplish the purpose of the visitor’s communication with us. Visitors can at all times decline to provide personally-identifying information, with the caution that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

We reveal potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information no more than to those of our employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using our website, you sanction to the transfer of such information to them. We will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. We disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of our website, third parties or the public at large. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

Though most modifications are likely to be trivial, we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to regularly check this page for any changes to our Privacy Policy.
